export const set2 = [
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  51</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["56", "55", "57", "58"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  34</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  3</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["36", "37", "38", "39"],
    answer: "37"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  56</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["58", "57", "59", "60"],
    answer: "58"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  84</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["85", "87", "86", "88"],
    answer: "86"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  63</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["66", "68", "67", "69"],
    answer: "67"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  23</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["29", "28", "30", "27"],
    answer: "29"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  63</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  1</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["62", "64", "63", "65"],
    answer: "64"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  32</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["35", "37", "36", "38"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  62</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["68", "70", "69", "71"],
    answer: "69"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  83</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["85", "84", "86", "87"],
    answer: "85"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  63</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["67", "68", "69", "70"],
    answer: "68"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  48</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  1</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["50", "49", "48", "47"],
    answer: "49"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  47</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  3</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["50", "49", "51", "48"],
    answer: "50"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  26</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  3</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["28", "30", "29", "27"],
    answer: "29"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  52</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["55", "56", "57", "58"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  73</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  6</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["78", "80", "79", "77"],
    answer: "79"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  45</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  3</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["48", "47", "49", "46"],
    answer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  24</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["27", "29", "28", "26"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  13</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["14", "15", "16", "13"],
    answer: "15"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  22</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  2</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["24", "23", "25", "26"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  25</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  5</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["29", "31", "30", "28"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  54</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  3</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["56", "57", "58", "55"],
    answer: "57"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  23</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  4</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["27", "26", "28", "25"],
    answer: "27"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  42</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["50", "48", "49", "51"],
    answer: "49"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="vertical-question">
          <div class="row">  33</div>
          <div class="row"><span class="op">+</span>  7</div>
          <div class="line">_____</div>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["39", "41", "40", "38"],
    answer: "40"
  }
];